laneige.com 2017-09-19

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy provides our policy and practice in connection with “personal information” or “personally identifiable information” (used interchangeably in this Privacy Policy) that AMOREPACIFIC US, INC. (“AMOREPACIFIC, we, us, or our”) may obtain from you when you communicate with us online or offline. The term “personal information” refers to the information connected to an individual person, such as name, physical address, date of birth, phone number, e-mail or another identifier that permits contacting of a specific person and other pieces of data that are maintained in personally identifiable form. 

We value your rights and respect your concerns about your privacy. Please read the following to understand the types of information we may collect about our customers, the ways we may use and share that information and the measures we take to protect your privacy and personal information. Your use of this website constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to the practices described below. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not cover information that you submit on other websites, even if there is a link to such outside website on this website, there is a link from an outside website to this website, or we communicate with you on those other websites. The information you submit to any other website is governed by the privacy policies of those websites.

1\. Information We Collect  
2\. How We Use the Information  
3\. How We Share the Information  
4\. Data Transfer  
5\. How We Protect Your Information  
6\. Your Rights and Choices  
7\. Tracking Technologies  
8\. Contacting Us  
9\. Changes to This Policy

  1. **Information We Collect**

We may obtain personal information about you on our website or at offline events. You may choose to provide personal information when you create an account or make a purchase on our website, subscribe to our electronic newsletter, participate at our offline event or contact us for customer service. The types of information you may provide to us include the following:

  * Name

  * Date of birth and gender

  * Username and password

  * Contact information (e.g., postal address, telephone number, mobile phone number, email address)

  * Payment information (e.g., PayPalTM account number, payment card number, expiration date, billing address)

  * Skincare concerns

  * Content you may provide to us (e.g., photographs, videos, reviews, comments and responses)

In addition, when you use our website, we may collect certain information about your activities on our website by automated means, such as cookies, IP addresses, browsing history and service history.

If you are under thirteen years of age, you may look at our website but may not provide personal information or make a purchase. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen.

  2. **How We Use the Information**

 We may use the personal information that we collect to provide you with products, information, and services; to process payment and access your purchase history; contact you regarding your purchases; communicating with you for account management and promotional purposes; and other matters related to your purchases and activities on our website. We may also contract with third-party advertising agencies, including the companies not affiliated with us, to send you information and promotional materials about our products based on the personal information we collect from you. We may also use your personal information to conduct, assess and improve our business operation, including: performing data analytics about our products and customers, detecting and preventing fraud, maintaining business systems and records, administering our electronic newsletter circulation system, and remaining in compliance with applicable laws and policies. We may also use the information in other ways for which a specific notice will be provided to you at the time of collection.

  3. **How We Share the Information**

 We may share your personal information with our corporate affiliates, such as Amorepacific Corporation, Amorepacific Group, and their subsidiaries and affiliates, for purposes of technical support and other business co-operations. We may share the information with third party service providers that perform services on our behalf according to our instructions, such as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mails or e-mails, analyzing customer data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, investigating fraudulent activities, conducting customer surveys and providing customer service. We do not authorize these third party companies to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. We may share your personal information with another company that buys some or all of our assets or shares, and that company may use and disclose personal information for purposes similar to what is described in this policy. We may also share and disclose your information with prospective business partners to evaluate a potential business transaction such as a merger or a joint venture.

In addition, we may share de-identified, aggregated information (i.e., the information that is not directly connected to your identity) about our customers with advertisers and marketing partners in order to gain insights about the market and improve our business performance. We may also contract with third party companies to collect information about your use of our website and other websites through technologies such as cookies, so that we may provide advertisements that are more relevant to your needs and interests based on your internet activity history. Those advertisements may appear either on our website, or on other websites.

We may disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government authorities when required by law or when we believe such disclosure is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss or to assist an investigation of any illegal activity, suspected or actual.

We will always take steps to ensure that any of your information used by all third parties is properly protected in accordance with this policy and applicable laws. We will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us outside the scope described herein without your consent.

  4. **Data Transfer**

 We may transfer the personal information we collect to the entities located in the countries other than the country in which the information is originally collected, including South Korea, where such entities administer and/or operate certain functions or services on our behalf, such as technical support, marketing assistance, data analytics and business administration. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as your country of residence, but we take reasonable measures at all times to protect the personal information in transmitting, retaining and processing the information as described in this policy. We will refuse to transfer personal information if we believe that the information will not receive reasonable protection.

  5. **How We Protect Your Information**

 We take the appropriate and necessary technical and administrative measures to protect your personal information against any unlawful or unauthorized access, disclosure, misappropriation, alteration or loss. However, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our website. Any transmission of your personal information is at your own risk.

  6. **Your Rights and Choices**

 You have the following rights and choices in providing your information and choosing how we communicate with you:

  * Updating or correcting your personal information: You can view and update the information you provide to us by logging into your online account and accessing “My Account” page

  * Opting out: You may choose not to receive marketing materials by clicking on “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any promotional e-mails you receive. 

  * Withdrawing consent and deleting your personal information: You may delete your information and withdraw your consent at any time by logging into your account and accessing “My Account” page on our website. You may do the same by contacting us.

  7. **Tracking Technologies**

Our website incorporates the technology to respond to your computer’s “do-not-track” signals; if you turn on the “do-not-track” option on your browser, our website will respect such request. 

Third parties that have content or services on our site may collect personal information about your browsing patterns or other online activities over time and across different sites when you use our website or service. These third parties do not change their tracking practices in response to “do-not-track” signals from your web browser and we do not obligate these parties to honor “do-not-track” signals.

  8. **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about our privacy or security practices, or if you would like to request access to or correction of your personal information, you can contact us at the following:

AMOREPACIFIC US, INC.   
1385 Broadway 10th FL. New York, NY 10018  

Your right to access or correct your personal information is subject to applicable legal restrictions. We may take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

If we need, or are required, to contact you concerning any event that involves your personal information, we may do so by e-mail, telephone, or mail. 

  9. **Changes to This Policy**

 We may revise this policy periodically and without prior notice to you. You should review our privacy policy periodically so that you remain up-to-date on our current practices and any changes to our policy. We will note the effective date of the latest version at the end of each policy.

Effective as of May 25, 2017. 

*“Cookies” are small amounts of information which we store on your computer. Unless you have indicated your objection when disclosing your details to us, our system will issue cookies to your computer when you log on to the site. Cookies make it easier for you to log on to and use the site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor website traffic and to personalize the content of the site for you. You may set up your computer to reject cookies by activating the settings on your browser although, in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our site. Please refer to the "Help" file of your Internet Browser to learn how to either block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored.
